[{"answer": "What is your problem", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And we don't have any bread", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't know you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I wasn't here last week", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How do you stay so calm", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " What do you mean in another life", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I think in another life, I handled dangerous explosives. I don't know", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't mean anything by it. Just an expression, isn't it?", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "They are just trying to get close to my friend so that they could get special treatment. Especially Therra", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "All I'm saying", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Get out of here! CLOSE THIS SECTION!!!!!!!!!", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "If it hadn't been for your quick action, many lives would have been lost", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Hopefully, there won't be a next time", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm sorry, my friend.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Feelings", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Feelings", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I remember feeling", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "No, for TOR.  I don't remember much, but I DO remember that", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "S", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You know something? We've got you as a hostage. I don't see a problem", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yep, you're right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Yeah, whatever.  YOU WANT PROOF?!?!?!?!?!", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No ice", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "He's from that place, you know. It's all coming back", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Beneath-The-Surface.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Sir", "qsentId": 30}]